How are you, brother?
Fine, sir.
Yes, where's your wife because I see you divorced - you have separated from your wife?
Yes.
It is not your will for this to happen.
It has happened, but you don't know how to go about it. This has affected you greatly.
Yes, sir.
I want to see you because it will be difficult for you to settle down because you are very disappointed.
Lately, you never believed that this divorce would lead to this.
Yes, sir.
It has affected your business - everything in your life.
What you are doing now is a funny thing.
Once you have said it, it's over because I see your relationship with this strange person
and this started from the internet and all that.
I want to see you. Please come and wait for me.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Testimony Time
Good Morning. My name is Childress Simmons Jr.
I'm from the United States of America.
I confirm the prophecy to be true.
I was married and I did get divorced.
I also did have a strange relationship on the internet.
Thank you very much. So can you share with us -
we want to learn from your experience and from what God Almighty has done in your life.
Can you share with us how this whole issue started - the strange relationship on the internet?
When I was around 7 or 8 years old, I remember going into my parents' room,
and there was a magazine with naked pictures although the breasts and the private part were covered.
I didn't see that magazine any time before that day or after that day - just that day.
As I got older around 11 to 12, my friends would bring pornographic pictures,
and I started looking at them.
Eventually my dad died when I was 10 and my mom remarried.
I went to stay with my step-father and my step-brother had libraries of pornographic magazines and DVDs.
My step-brother loved me but he just didn't see anything wrong with that.
I would spend hours watching and looking at those magazines.
So this was right from the young age of 7 or 8 years old
that pornography started entering into your life, is that right?
Yes, sir.
So from there, how did the addiction to pornography really take hold and
begin to affect your life in all areas?
Eventually, you get an appetite for it.
As I got older, when circumstances would become hard,
I would just automatically use pornography as a pacifier.
It was there to pacify me in my hardship.
As I continued to mature and grow, the pornography got more perverted.
When you get on the internet, you click on it,
it would just give you galleries of different categories
and you can click on whatever you want.
I would watch whatever would stimulate me and spend hours at a time doing it.
I would stay up all night and then go to work.
It's by the grace of God I didn't die because I would fall asleep driving on the road.
God spared my life.
So the man of God mentioned that this addiction to pornography,
the strange relationship on the internet,
started affecting your business, your career and everything about you.
Apart from like you said in driving, how else did it affect your job?
Well, in the job I wasn't focused on doing my job to the best of my ability.
My focus was gone. I spent all night masturbating,
and so I really didn't have the energy to do my job to the best of my ability.
Okay sir, what happened before you married your wife? How did the addiction to pornography
affect the beginning of the relationship and ultimately the divorce we heard about?
When you are watching porn, it changes your mindset on how you look at women.
You don't look at women from the inside out but from the outside in.
You look at them like a dessert.
Instead of getting to know a person,
you would experiment or have sexual relationships; then you would get married.
That's not the way you are supposed to start a union.
What were your thoughts the time that you said okay, let me try and get married?
Was it as a way of escaping from pornography or what was the thought behind that?
I thought that as it was a sexual problem, if I had a wife, it would go away.
You can have sex with your wife and be satisfied and you can satisfy her.
But there's a different appetite that must be satisfied that comes over you.
You are driven to do it; it's like you are compelled to fulfill that appetite.
Once you are done, you feel exhausted; you may cry and pray
but it seems that something just takes over.
So after your first marriage, how did the pornography affect the marriage?
Was it still continuing during your marriage with your first wife?
Yes, as with my first wife, in a marital relationship, if you are not friends,
you become alienated from each other.
She would go her way and you would go your way,
leaving you all the time in the world to masturbate,
watch porn, do whatever you want because there is no union.
So, yes, it affected my first relationship.
So tell us, how did that then move on and end the relationship - ending in a divorce?
Eventually, as the saying goes, 'If it starts badly, it will end badly'.
That's what happened; it started badly and ended badly.
We severed the relationship but I didn't get deliverance.
I married again and I had the same problem.
After the first divorce, what then happened in terms of this pornography?
Did it go up another level? Did it get worse?
It basically stayed the same.
After I got married the second time, the relationship was very uncomfortable.
It wasn't friendly; then it got worse.
I started going on the internet and spent more time on it than ever before.
So what was your thought in getting married the second time,
after you saw that marriage couldn't actually solve this problem the first time?
What was on your mind when going into the second marriage?
I went to church and I thought I was well.
So, I thought I would give it another try and we could have a blessed marriage.
But what I realised was that I needed deliverance,
as you can't have a sincere mind without spiritual deliverance.
Thank you very much. At this time, did you never say, "Enough is enough.
I don't want pornography anymore" or you were just happy with it in your life?
Oh no, I wasn't happy with it because I was exhausting my body.
I was up all night and sometimes, I would come home from work
and have the desire to do it too.
I knew I was killing myself.
But at the same time, there was nothing I could do about it.
During my second marriage, I started searching the internet for solution
and that was when I saw Emmanuel TV.
Alright, sir. Before we hear more about Emmanuel TV,
tell us, what other ways or efforts did you make to stop this habit of pornography and masturbation?
I fasted, received prayers, got an internet filter and did various things to stop
but you cannot stop externally.
When people say just stop it, I don't believe that.
It has to stop spiritually and you need deliverance.
So you mean that even if at a time you stopped yourself physically,
you would still fall back into it again? There would still be an urge?
Definitely, I noticed that every six months I would get a strong appetite to consume it.
Then, after the six months I could be okay and think everything was good.
Then, it would come again very strong.
So, the second marriage you then went into,
how was the relationship any different or was there no difference - just like the first one?
The difference between the two was that the women were different.
So, they were different experiences.
But as far as the affection went, they both turned out the same way.
Something came to change the way we looked at each other and cared for each other,
which left doors open for pornography and perversion.
And you think this spirit of pornograhpy and masturbation was behind
that loss of affection and separation once again?
I know because it has been a root in me since I was young.
So, I think it was the main leader of everything that went wrong in my life.
So, after this second marriage also ended in a divorce,
what then happened after that?
After that, you reach your lowest point because you have divorced again
and you're wondering, "What's happening, what is wrong with me?"
Then, I started consuming more from pictures, to videos, to live camera,
that's when there is another person you are looking at and
you engage in sexual activities.
Is that person necessarily in your area or neighbourhood or where could that person be?
From all over the world, all you have to do is click on a particular photo
and that person can be anywhere - Germany, Australia - and you engage over the camera.
So this is how you had gone from pornographic magazines, up to videos,
up to the internet, and now finally, to having sex via a web cam with somebody.
Was the desire never satisfied up until this point?
The desire is never satisfied, it grows.
It grows stronger and it gets perverted because what you used to watch,
you can't watch it anymore because it doesn't satisfy you,
so you have to watch something else or do something else.
So at this time, you were facing divorce.
What kind of relationships were you having with women at that time?
After my divorce?
Yes.
After my divorce, during my second marriage, I saw Emmanuel TV.
That was when I realised that a person could be housing demons.
Even though I knew I had issues, I wouldn't mess with a woman, no matter how pretty she was.
I just realised that she could be housing demons in her.
I wouldn't mess with a woman or person.
Ok. So then tell us, from that area of going into webcam,
did you ever have the mind of wanting to meet any of these women
you were seeing on the screen personally?
What then happened after that
in terms of your addiction to pornography and these strange relationships?
After you keep seeing pornography over and over,
you have images to manifest or duplicate.
Yes, it came to a point in time when I wanted to meet escorts
but deep down inside me, I knew it was the death of me if I was to go out.
The desire came but I just couldn't do it.
During this time that you had been introduced or initiated into this pornography and masturbation,
what kind of women would it be pushing you towards
or what kind of women would be coming your way that you would be seeing?
It never drew me to any type of physical relationship.
Physically, when I looked at a woman, I might lust after her
but I never wanted to live with her.
It was always spiritually or mentally where the perversion would take place for me.
Thank you very much.
That was then how you started searching
and as you said, you found Emmanuel TV.
What gave you hope in Emmanuel TV?
What was it that brought about your coming here today?
I have seen people dealing with the same issue.
When you go to a church and talk about your issue, nobody responds back.
It makes it seem something is really wrong with you.
When I saw Emmanuel TV, I thought I could go and get help.
That drove me to come and get deliverance.
Ok, sir. Tell us again, what was the state of your mind at this time
before you finally came to The SCOAN?
What were the kind of dreams you were then having
and how did this affect you spiritually?
Spiritually, I started seeing spirits in my dreams, dealing with sexual immorality.
It started affecting me in the spiritual realm.
Alright, thank you very much, sir.
Lastly, before we hear about when you came to The SCOAN,
can you tell us about the women that you married
and the kind of women you had relationships with.
Were they the kind of people that you had thought, "Yes, this is the kind of person I want to marry",
or was there anything else about those two marriages you had?
When you are influenced by watching porn, you see women in a bad light -
I mean, not in the true light.
I was drawn physically to them but not to what was on the inside.
I would marry them based on how they looked.
What kind of women were they?
They had prior marriages and children.
I was always led to those type of women.
So the kind of women that came into your life because of that spirit
were people that had also had previous relationships or divorces and also had children.
Those were the kind of people you ended up marrying?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Finally then, you came to The SCOAN and we saw what happened.
You received a word of prophecy and your deliverance.
Tell us, what was that experience like and how are you feeling now after the deliverance?
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed,
prior to that, I had prayed, "Lord, if he just says a word, I know I am delivered".
At the prayer line, he hit me three times on my chest.
He came back and hit me two more times.
I didn't feel any fire or anything.
I want that to be known because I think sometimes, we become oversensualised.
But I just believed and I knew that I was made whole.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Truly, believing is the condition and as long as we believe, we are blessed.
So as you are blessed and delivered now,
tell us, what have the changes been since last week till this week?
My heart.
The grace of God on my heart
and how I see women - I don't look at them as physical objects.
They are daughters of God and are to be respected.
Glory be to God. Let's put our hands together for Jesus once again!
Once your heart is changed, everything about you is changed.
So I want to ask you about the prophecy that the man of God gave to you, sir.
Can you remind us of some of the points that the man of God said and
how they are really true for your life and what it was like at that time receiving this word of prophecy?
When he prophesied about the divorce, that was recent.
Nobody knew about that strange relationship on the internet.
God located me and I thank God for that.
It blessed me.
Glory be to God. One of the last points that the man of God said in his prophecy
was, how you had had such disappointments and you had never thought
that your life could come down to this level.
What do you have to say about that?
As a young man, I excelled in everything I put my mind to.
I was at the lowest point as a man - I mean, rock bottom.
That was very true. I was hopeless.
I thank God for my sister; she spoke life to me.
She said, "Your latter shall be greater".
I thank God for that.
And that was how you came here and God Almighty met you at that very lowest point in your life.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
So, sir, now as a changed man,
someone that has passed through the valley of the shadow of death,
and has come out stronger, what is your advice to viewers watching you all over the world,
specifically first of all for those who may be still suffering from a similar vice
to the one you found yourself in?
Don't take it lightly because this world pushes pornography, fornication and all that.
When you enter into that, you are opening yourself for the demons
and it is going to corrupt your heart.
If you die in that state, you will be tormented in hell.
Give your life to God and let God clean your heart and serve Him.
Thank you very much.
Mr Childress Simmons Jr.
Prophecy Confirmation
We would also like you to give a word of advice to parents
because you mentioned that this happened in your parents' house at the age of 7 or 8 years old.
That was the first exposure you had to pornography. What advice can you give?
Back then, we didn't have technology.
So, be careful of the books and things you have.
Now, you have TV, movies and the internet.
So, you really need to guard what your children are watching to protect their souls.
Alright. Thank you very much.
Lastly, to viewers all over the world, about the power of God Almighty
that is still working, that delivered you. What can you say about this power?
God is still a Deliverer
because I would never have thought I would be where I am right now.
I feel renewed.
I feel restored.
I know I am a child of God. I know I am redeemed.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
We can see something in your hands right now.
Can you tell us what this is and how this has been helping you?
This is the Faith Bracelet I use to meditate on the Word of God.
It really puts the Word of God in my heart
and it guides me throughout the day.
Hallelujah. So now, you are no longer thinking lustful thoughts or of pornography
or how to go and browse on the internet?
That's true because a dream came to me the other night of various women.
As soon as I saw their faces, I didn't look at their bodies, I just woke up.
But before, how would you have reacted in such a dream?
I would have gone on with the dream - continued it.
This is a confirmation that it is over in spirit and in truth.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Put your hands together for Jesus!
Mr Childress Simmons Jr.
Prophecy Confirmation
So the last thing we want to hear from you, sir,
how are you feeling now? Are you fulfilled in your visit here?
Yes, I am fulfilled. I feel that I am a redeemed son of God.
Glory be to God. We encourage you, sir, truly you are delivered by the Word of God,
now make God's Word the standard for your life
and for all those whose lives are centered in Christ Jesus,
better is not good enough, the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019